大家好，欢迎收看 AI Weekly 第001期。我是你们的AI主播。
本周AI领域发生了不少值得关注的事情，让我们一起来看看。
导语: 本周TechCrunch AI报道了一则重要消息。
正文: It's only the latest of several side projects that the AI startup has ditched over the past week.
点评: 这无疑是AI领域的一个重要进展，值得我们持续关注。
导语: 本周The Verge AI报道了一则重要消息。
正文: After Anthropic updated its tool for copying another AI's memory into Claude earlier this month, Google Gemini is rolling out new "Import Memory" and "Import Chat History" features on desktop that can help users quickly copy over everything their current AI already knows about them. To use the "Import Memory" tool, users copy and paste [&#8230;]
点评: 这无疑是AI领域的一个重要进展，值得我们持续关注。
导语: 本周The Verge AI报道了一则重要消息。
正文: Apple's iOS 27 update will allow users to choose the AI chatbot they want to link with Siri. That's according to a report from Bloomberg's Mark Gurman, who says third-party chatbots downloaded from the App Store, like Google's Gemini or Anthropic's Claude, will be able to fetch replies for Siri - similar to how the [&#8230;]
点评: 这无疑是AI领域的一个重要进展，值得我们持续关注。
导语: 本周MIT Technology Review AI报道了一则重要消息。
正文: AI is at war. Anthropic and the Pentagon feuded over how to weaponize Anthropic’s AI model Claude; then OpenAI swept the Pentagon off its feet with an “opportunistic and sloppy” deal. Users quit ChatGPT in droves. People marched through London in the biggest protest against AI to date. If you’re keeping score, Anthropic—the company founded&#8230;
点评: 这无疑是AI领域的一个重要进展，值得我们持续关注。
导语: 本周TechCrunch AI报道了一则重要消息。
正文: The model, which lets enterprises build voice agents for sales and customer engagement, puts Mistral in direct competition with the likes of ElevenLabs, Deepgram, and OpenAI.
点评: 这无疑是AI领域的一个重要进展，值得我们持续关注。
导语: 本周Ars Technica AI报道了一则重要消息。
正文: OpenAI's new GPT‑5.3‑Codex‑Spark is 15 times faster at coding than its predecessor.
点评: 这无疑是AI领域的一个重要进展，值得我们持续关注。
导语: 本周TechCrunch AI报道了一则重要消息。
正文: Google is launching Lyria 3 Pro, an upgraded music model that generates longer, more customizable tracks, as it expands AI music tools across Gemini, enterprise products, and other services.
点评: 这无疑是AI领域的一个重要进展，值得我们持续关注。
导语: 本周TechCrunch AI报道了一则重要消息。
正文: A federal judge has ordered that the Trump administration rescind recent restrictions it placed on the AI company.
点评: 这无疑是AI领域的一个重要进展，值得我们持续关注。
以上就是本周的AI资讯，如果你觉得有帮助，请点赞关注。
我们下期再见！